http://www.travelgrove.com/privacy_policy.php

compare & save flights hotels cars vacations cruises deals travel guides tips community forum blog  Travelgrove's Privacy Policy: We only store personal information at Travelgrove if you choose to.We currently store users' email addresses who have chosen to sign up for our newsletter. We are NOT selling or sharing this information with any third parties and use the newsletter to promote our "Grovezine - Fresh Picked Weekly Deals". Anybody signing up, can unsubscribe from our newsletter and we do not allow double sign ups in order to eliminate spamming and mail bombing. We also run a travel forum, which stores your email address for validation purposes. We do NOT send out any promotional materials to users signing up to the forums unless they select that they want to receive a newsletter.We are also currently working on a member section. Once the member section is complete we will be saving the necessary personal information that you submit, so that you may log into our member section. As a member of Travelgrove Inc, you will be in complete control of your travel-planning needs. This includes controlling the use of information you provide to Travelgrove Inc. We fully understand and respect the privacy of our customers and will keep committed to do so in the future.Because protecting your privacy is important to us, you can be assured that Travelgrove discloses the following:What personal information is being gathered about you and how the information will be usedWith whom the information will be shared (if anyone)An opt-out policyAccess to your information (including how to update or correct inaccuracies)Other information about your privacyWhat personal information is being gathered by Travelgrove and how is this information being used?Member RegistrationWhen you become a Travelgrove Inc member you provide your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address which will be your log-in name a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including: (i) personal identification; (ii) to customize the content of our site to meet your specific needs; and (iii) to make product improvements to Travelgrove. In addition, your e-mail address is collected to send you an e-mail message confirming your new member registration. As a member you will occasionally receive updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new Travelgrove Inc services, and other noteworthy news items. However, you may always decline to receive these e-mail messages.Member ProfileMembers will be selecting their site preferences and will be able to post additional information that we will use to auto-fill out 3rd party forms (whenever you make a reservation). We will not share this information with any 3rd party unless you request it.GROVEZINETravelgrove Inc's GROVEZINE is an optional service to members that will keep you updated, we will try to customized each and every newsletter to fit your profile.Online SurveysTravelgrove Inc values opinions and comments from members, so we will frequently conduct online surveys. These surveys are entirely optional for all members. Typically, the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to Travelgrove.com and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for members. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.CookiesIn order to track whether you are a first time user or not we cookie everybody coming to the site. We do not store any personal information on this cookie. However, we will be using cookies for our member section as well as our advertiser section where we will need to store limited personal information for your login, if you choose so.Who will the information be shared with, if anyone?No data will be passed on to third parties whom you will be booking from.We do not sell individual customer names or other private profile information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future.Opt Out PolicyYou will be able to unsubscribe from our newsletter anytime, directly through the email you got into your mailbox.As a member of Travelgrove's Community you will occasionally receive e-mail updates from us about fare sales in your area, special offers, new Travelgrove Inc services, and other noteworthy news items. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, please contact us at member(at)Travelgrove.com. Travelgrove Inc reserves the right to limit membership to those who will accept e-mails. Members will be notified via e-mail prior to any actions taken.How can you access, update or correct your information?At any time, you can view and/or update your GROVEZINE subscriptions. You can also update your personal profile, which includes member registration and travel preferences information, through the "My Account" link, accessible through the "My Grove" link on our home page at www.Travelgrove.com.What other information should I know about my privacy?Travelgrove contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which Travelgrove has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from Travelgrove's Privacy Statement. Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you're online.
In addition to the circumstances described above, Travelgrove Inc may disclose member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Travelgrove Inc or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.
Any material changes in the way Travelgrove Inc uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices to info(at)travelgrove.com. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. Travelgrove Inc will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt.back to top
Travelgrove InfoAbout usPartner listAdvertisingUseful hintsTerms of usePrivacyContactAffiliatesFAQTravel ThemesBook Your Summer Vacation Early this Year NEW!Easter and Spring Break GetawaysBlooming West Spring GetawaysHeat Things Up this Valentine's DayFresh powder is falling! Plan your Colorado ski vacation today!GroveZineFresh picked travel deals!Sign up now FREE!previewsubmitTravel ToolsTravel GuidesTravel Forum   Welcome to Travelgrove login register tell a friend bookmark it  Select language: enes   popular flights | destination reviews | about us | advertising | partners | affiliates | FAQ | privacy | terms of service | travel insurance | frequent flyer© Copyright 2004 - 2020 Travelgrove, Inc.All rights reservedTravelgrove Inc is not responsible for content on external Web sites.Visit our international sites:travelgrove.comtravelgrove.ittravelgrove.co.uktravelgrove.estravelgrove.detravelgrove.frOther sites we like:Metafares.com Travengo.com Travelgrove newswhat's happening on travelgroveQuestions about how to use Travelgroveread our F.A.Q. for helpTell us your opinionhelp travelgrove improve
